- ObjectiveID: 99F_MSQ_ER_GatherAllies
  Type: MainStoryQuest
  Difficulty: ""
  DifficultyLevel: 58.0
  MaxInfluenceLevel: ""
  FlagPvp: ""
  CanBeShared: ""
  CanFastTravel: ""
  Task: 99F_MSQ_ER_GatherAllies_container
  NpcDestinationId: 99F_Sun_03
  ExclusiveTerritory: ""
  AchievementId: 99F_MSQ_01
  RequiredAchievementId: 99E_MSQ_10 || 99_MSQ_56
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
  SuccessGameEventId: 99F_MSQ_ER_GatherAllies_success
  FailureGameEventId: ""
  ProgressionReward: ""
  ExperienceReward: ""
  ObjectiveReward: ""
  ItemRewardName: PotionHealthT4
  ItemRewardQty: 5.0
  ShouldResetOnFactionChange: ""
  Repeatable: ""
  CanBeAbandoned: false
  Title: "@99F_MSQ01_GatherAllies_title"
  Description: "@99F_MSQ01_GatherAllies_desc"
  PlayerPrompt: "@99F_MSQ01_GatherAllies_start_prompt"
  ObjectiveProposalResponse: "@99F_MSQ01_GatherAllies_proposal"
  InProgressResponse: "@99F_MSQ01_GatherAllies_incomplete"
  DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt: "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
  DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse: "@99F_MSQ01_GatherAllies_complete"
  ObjectiveCompletionResponse: ""
  ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse: ""
  HideIncompleteTurninMarker: true
  ORMReleaseEventTags: ""
  ORMReleaseActiveOverride: ""
  SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid: ""
  EntitlementId: ""
  QuestArcTag: ""
  HideAvailableMapIcon: ""
  NOTE: ""
- ObjectiveID: 99F_MSQ_ER_MeetWiseman
  Type: MainStoryQuest
  Difficulty: ""
  DifficultyLevel: 58.0
  MaxInfluenceLevel: ""
  FlagPvp: ""
  CanBeShared: ""
  CanFastTravel: ""
  Task: 99F_MSQ_ER_MeetWiseman_container
  NpcDestinationId: 99F_Grace_04
  ExclusiveTerritory: ""
  AchievementId: 99F_MSQ_02
  RequiredAchievementId: 99F_MSQ_01
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
  SuccessGameEventId: 99F_MSQ_ER_MeetWiseman_success
  FailureGameEventId: ""
  ProgressionReward: ""
  ExperienceReward: ""
  ObjectiveReward: ""
  ItemRewardName: CRX_RewardContainerT5_Legwear_60
  ItemRewardQty: 1.0
  ShouldResetOnFactionChange: ""
  Repeatable: ""
  CanBeAbandoned: false
  Title: "@99F_MSQ02_MeetWiseman_title"
  Description: "@99F_MSQ02_MeetWiseman_desc"
  PlayerPrompt: "@99F_MSQ02_MeetWiseman_start_prompt"
  ObjectiveProposalResponse: "@99F_MSQ02_MeetWiseman_proposal"
  InProgressResponse: "@99F_MSQ02_MeetWiseman_incomplete"
  DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt: "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
  DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse: "@99F_MSQ02_MeetWiseman_complete"
  ObjectiveCompletionResponse: ""
  ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse: ""
  HideIncompleteTurninMarker: true
  ORMReleaseEventTags: ""
  ORMReleaseActiveOverride: ""
  SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid: ""
  EntitlementId: ""
  QuestArcTag: ""
  HideAvailableMapIcon: ""
  NOTE: ""
- ObjectiveID: 99F_MSQ_ER_CreateRefuge
  Type: MainStoryQuest
  Difficulty: ""
  DifficultyLevel: 58.0
  MaxInfluenceLevel: ""
  FlagPvp: ""
  CanBeShared: ""
  CanFastTravel: ""
  Task: 99F_MSQ_ER_CreateRefuge_container
  NpcDestinationId: 99F_Sun_04
  ExclusiveTerritory: ""
  AchievementId: 99F_MSQ_03
  RequiredAchievementId: 99F_MSQ_02
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
  SuccessGameEventId: 99F_MSQ_ER_CreateRefuge_success
  FailureGameEventId: ""
  ProgressionReward: ""
  ExperienceReward: ""
  ObjectiveReward: ""
  ItemRewardName: CRX_RewardContainerT5_Weapons_60
  ItemRewardQty: 1.0
  ShouldResetOnFactionChange: ""
  Repeatable: ""
  CanBeAbandoned: false
  Title: "@99F_MSQ03_CreateRefuge_title"
  Description: "@99F_MSQ03_CreateRefuge_desc"
  PlayerPrompt: "@99F_MSQ03_CreateRefuge_start_prompt"
  ObjectiveProposalResponse: "@99F_MSQ03_CreateRefuge_proposal"
  InProgressResponse: "@99F_MSQ03_CreateRefuge_incomplete"
  DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt: "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
  DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse: "@99F_MSQ03_CreateRefuge_complete"
  ObjectiveCompletionResponse: ""
  ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse: ""
  HideIncompleteTurninMarker: true
  ORMReleaseEventTags: ""
  ORMReleaseActiveOverride: ""
  SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid: ""
  EntitlementId: ""
  QuestArcTag: ""
  HideAvailableMapIcon: ""
  NOTE: ""
- ObjectiveID: 99F_MSQ_ER_InspireAllies
  Type: MainStoryQuest
  Difficulty: ""
  DifficultyLevel: 58.0
  MaxInfluenceLevel: ""
  FlagPvp: ""
  CanBeShared: ""
  CanFastTravel: ""
  Task: 99F_MSQ_ER_InspireAllies_container
  NpcDestinationId: 99F_Sun_04a
  ExclusiveTerritory: ""
  AchievementId: 99F_MSQ_04
  RequiredAchievementId: 99F_MSQ_03
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
  SuccessGameEventId: 99F_MSQ_ER_InspireAllies_success
  FailureGameEventId: ""
  ProgressionReward: ""
  ExperienceReward: ""
  ObjectiveReward: ""
  ItemRewardName: HoningStoneT4
  ItemRewardQty: 3.0
  ShouldResetOnFactionChange: ""
  Repeatable: ""
  CanBeAbandoned: false
  Title: "@99F_MSQ04_InspireAllies_title"
  Description: "@99F_MSQ04_InspireAllies_desc"
  PlayerPrompt: "@99F_MSQ04_InspireAllies_start_prompt"
  ObjectiveProposalResponse: "@99F_MSQ04_InspireAllies_proposal"
  InProgressResponse: "@99F_MSQ04_InspireAllies_incomplete"
  DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt: "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
  DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse: "@99F_MSQ04_InspireAllies_complete"
  ObjectiveCompletionResponse: ""
  ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse: ""
  HideIncompleteTurninMarker: true
  ORMReleaseEventTags: ""
  ORMReleaseActiveOverride: ""
  SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid: ""
  EntitlementId: ""
  QuestArcTag: ""
  HideAvailableMapIcon: ""
  NOTE: ""
- ObjectiveID: 99F_MSQ_ER_MeetEmpress
  Type: MainStoryQuest
  Difficulty: ""
  DifficultyLevel: 59.0
  MaxInfluenceLevel: ""
  FlagPvp: ""
  CanBeShared: ""
  CanFastTravel: ""
  Task: 99F_MSQ_ER_MeetEmpress_container
  NpcDestinationId: 99F_Empress_01
  ExclusiveTerritory: ""
  AchievementId: 99F_MSQ_05
  RequiredAchievementId: 99F_MSQ_04
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
  SuccessGameEventId: 99F_MSQ_ER_MeetEmpress_success
  FailureGameEventId: ""
  ProgressionReward: ""
  ExperienceReward: ""
  ObjectiveReward: ""
  ItemRewardName: CRX_RewardContainerT5_Footwear_60
  ItemRewardQty: 1.0
  ShouldResetOnFactionChange: ""
  Repeatable: ""
  CanBeAbandoned: false
  Title: "@99F_MSQ05_MeetEmpress_title"
  Description: "@99F_MSQ05_MeetEmpress_desc"
  PlayerPrompt: "@99F_MSQ05_MeetEmpress_start_prompt"
  ObjectiveProposalResponse: "@99F_MSQ05_MeetEmpress_proposal"
  InProgressResponse: "@99F_MSQ05_MeetEmpress_incomplete"
  DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt: "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
  DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse: "@99F_MSQ05_MeetEmpress_complete"
  ObjectiveCompletionResponse: ""
  ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse: ""
  HideIncompleteTurninMarker: true
  ORMReleaseEventTags: ""
  ORMReleaseActiveOverride: ""
  SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid: ""
  EntitlementId: ""
  QuestArcTag: ""
  HideAvailableMapIcon: ""
  NOTE: ""
- ObjectiveID: 99F_MSQ_ER_AscendPeak
  Type: MainStoryQuest
  Difficulty: ""
  DifficultyLevel: 59.0
  MaxInfluenceLevel: ""
  FlagPvp: ""
  CanBeShared: ""
  CanFastTravel: ""
  Task: 99F_MSQ_ER_AscendPeak_container
  NpcDestinationId: 99F_Empress_01a
  ExclusiveTerritory: ""
  AchievementId: 99F_MSQ_06
  RequiredAchievementId: 99F_MSQ_05
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
  SuccessGameEventId: 99F_MSQ_ER_AscendPeak_success
  FailureGameEventId: ""
  ProgressionReward: ""
  ExperienceReward: ""
  ObjectiveReward: ""
  ItemRewardName: CRX_RewardContainerT5_Chestwear_60
  ItemRewardQty: 1.0
  ShouldResetOnFactionChange: ""
  Repeatable: ""
  CanBeAbandoned: false
  Title: "@99F_MSQ06_AscendPeak_title"
  Description: "@99F_MSQ06_AscendPeak_desc"
  PlayerPrompt: "@99F_MSQ06_AscendPeak_start_prompt"
  ObjectiveProposalResponse: "@99F_MSQ06_AscendPeak_proposal"
  InProgressResponse: "@99F_MSQ06_AscendPeak_incomplete"
  DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt: "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
  DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse: "@99F_MSQ06_AscendPeak_complete"
  ObjectiveCompletionResponse: ""
  ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse: ""
  HideIncompleteTurninMarker: true
  ORMReleaseEventTags: ""
  ORMReleaseActiveOverride: ""
  SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid: ""
  EntitlementId: ""
  QuestArcTag: ""
  HideAvailableMapIcon: ""
  NOTE: ""
- ObjectiveID: 99F_MSQ_ER_CreateIncense
  Type: MainStoryQuest
  Difficulty: ""
  DifficultyLevel: 59.0
  MaxInfluenceLevel: ""
  FlagPvp: ""
  CanBeShared: ""
  CanFastTravel: ""
  Task: 99F_MSQ_ER_CreateIncense_container
  NpcDestinationId: 99F_Sun_05a
  ExclusiveTerritory: ""
  AchievementId: 99F_MSQ_07
  RequiredAchievementId: 99F_MSQ_06
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
  SuccessGameEventId: 99F_MSQ_ER_CreateIncense_success
  FailureGameEventId: ""
  ProgressionReward: ""
  ExperienceReward: ""
  ObjectiveReward: ""
  ItemRewardName: PotionHealthT4
  ItemRewardQty: 10.0
  ShouldResetOnFactionChange: ""
  Repeatable: ""
  CanBeAbandoned: false
  Title: "@99F_MSQ07_CreateIncense_title"
  Description: "@99F_MSQ07_CreateIncense_desc"
  PlayerPrompt: "@99F_MSQ07_CreateIncense_start_prompt"
  ObjectiveProposalResponse: "@99F_MSQ07_CreateIncense_proposal"
  InProgressResponse: "@99F_MSQ07_CreateIncense_incomplete"
  DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt: "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
  DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse: "@99F_MSQ07_CreateIncense_complete"
  ObjectiveCompletionResponse: ""
  ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse: ""
  HideIncompleteTurninMarker: true
  ORMReleaseEventTags: ""
  ORMReleaseActiveOverride: ""
  SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid: ""
  EntitlementId: ""
  QuestArcTag: ""
  HideAvailableMapIcon: ""
  NOTE: ""
- ObjectiveID: 99F_MSQ_ER_FightLiang
  Type: MainStoryQuest
  Difficulty: ""
  DifficultyLevel: 59.0
  MaxInfluenceLevel: ""
  FlagPvp: ""
  CanBeShared: ""
  CanFastTravel: ""
  Task: 99F_MSQ_ER_FightLiang_container
  NpcDestinationId: 99F_Liang_01
  ExclusiveTerritory: ""
  AchievementId: 99F_MSQ_08
  RequiredAchievementId: 99F_MSQ_07 && !Archetype_Mercenary && !Archetype_Warmonger && !Archetype_Tracker && !Archetype_Musketeer && !Archetype_Occultist && !Archetype_Theurgist && !Archetype_Wanderer
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
  SuccessGameEventId: 99F_MSQ_ER_FightLiang_success
  FailureGameEventId: ""
  ProgressionReward: ""
  ExperienceReward: ""
  ObjectiveReward: ""
  ItemRewardName: CRX_RewardContainerT5_Weapons_60
  ItemRewardQty: 1.0
  ShouldResetOnFactionChange: ""
  Repeatable: ""
  CanBeAbandoned: false
  Title: "@99F_MSQ08_FightLiang_title"
  Description: "@99F_MSQ08_FightLiang_desc"
  PlayerPrompt: "@99F_MSQ08_FightLiang_start_prompt"
  ObjectiveProposalResponse: "@99F_MSQ08_FightLiang_proposal"
  InProgressResponse: "@99F_MSQ08_FightLiang_incomplete"
  DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt: "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
  DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse: "@99F_MSQ08_FightLiang_complete"
  ObjectiveCompletionResponse: ""
  ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse: ""
  HideIncompleteTurninMarker: true
  ORMReleaseEventTags: ""
  ORMReleaseActiveOverride: ""
  SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid: ""
  EntitlementId: ""
  QuestArcTag: ""
  HideAvailableMapIcon: ""
  NOTE: Soul Trial
- ObjectiveID: 99F_MSQ_ER_FightLiang_destroyer
  Type: MainStoryQuest
  Difficulty: ""
  DifficultyLevel: 59.0
  MaxInfluenceLevel: ""
  FlagPvp: ""
  CanBeShared: ""
  CanFastTravel: ""
  Task: 99F_MSQ_ER_FightLiang_container
  NpcDestinationId: 99F_Liang_01
  ExclusiveTerritory: ""
  AchievementId: 99F_MSQ_08
  RequiredAchievementId: 99F_MSQ_07 && Archetype_Warmonger
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
  SuccessGameEventId: 99F_MSQ_ER_FightLiang_success_destroyer
  FailureGameEventId: ""
  ProgressionReward: ""
  ExperienceReward: ""
  ObjectiveReward: ""
  ItemRewardName: CRX_RewardContainerT5_Handwear_60
  ItemRewardQty: 1.0
  ShouldResetOnFactionChange: ""
  Repeatable: ""
  CanBeAbandoned: false
  Title: "@99F_MSQ08_FightLiang_title"
  Description: "@99F_MSQ08_FightLiang_desc"
  PlayerPrompt: "@99F_MSQ08_FightLiang_start_prompt"
  ObjectiveProposalResponse: "@99F_MSQ08_FightLiang_proposal"
  InProgressResponse: "@99F_MSQ08_FightLiang_incomplete"
  DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt: "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
  DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse: "@99F_MSQ08_FightLiang_complete"
  ObjectiveCompletionResponse: ""
  ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse: ""
  HideIncompleteTurninMarker: true
  ORMReleaseEventTags: ""
  ORMReleaseActiveOverride: ""
  SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid: ""
  EntitlementId: ""
  QuestArcTag: ""
  HideAvailableMapIcon: ""
  NOTE: Soul Trial alt
- ObjectiveID: 99F_MSQ_ER_FightLiang_musketeer
  Type: MainStoryQuest
  Difficulty: ""
  DifficultyLevel: 59.0
  MaxInfluenceLevel: ""
  FlagPvp: ""
  CanBeShared: ""
  CanFastTravel: ""
  Task: 99F_MSQ_ER_FightLiang_container
  NpcDestinationId: 99F_Liang_01
  ExclusiveTerritory: ""
  AchievementId: 99F_MSQ_08
  RequiredAchievementId: 99F_MSQ_07 && Archetype_Musketeer
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
  SuccessGameEventId: 99F_MSQ_ER_FightLiang_success_musketeer
  FailureGameEventId: ""
  ProgressionReward: ""
  ExperienceReward: ""
  ObjectiveReward: ""
  ItemRewardName: CRX_RewardContainerT5_Handwear_60
  ItemRewardQty: 1.0
  ShouldResetOnFactionChange: ""
  Repeatable: ""
  CanBeAbandoned: false
  Title: "@99F_MSQ08_FightLiang_title"
  Description: "@99F_MSQ08_FightLiang_desc"
  PlayerPrompt: "@99F_MSQ08_FightLiang_start_prompt"
  ObjectiveProposalResponse: "@99F_MSQ08_FightLiang_proposal"
  InProgressResponse: "@99F_MSQ08_FightLiang_incomplete"
  DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt: "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
  DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse: "@99F_MSQ08_FightLiang_complete"
  ObjectiveCompletionResponse: ""
  ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse: ""
  HideIncompleteTurninMarker: true
  ORMReleaseEventTags: ""
  ORMReleaseActiveOverride: ""
  SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid: ""
  EntitlementId: ""
  QuestArcTag: ""
  HideAvailableMapIcon: ""
  NOTE: Soul Trial alt
- ObjectiveID: 99F_MSQ_ER_FightLiang_mystic
  Type: MainStoryQuest
  Difficulty: ""
  DifficultyLevel: 59.0
  MaxInfluenceLevel: ""
  FlagPvp: ""
  CanBeShared: ""
  CanFastTravel: ""
  Task: 99F_MSQ_ER_FightLiang_container
  NpcDestinationId: 99F_Liang_01
  ExclusiveTerritory: ""
  AchievementId: 99F_MSQ_08
  RequiredAchievementId: 99F_MSQ_07 && Archetype_Theurgist
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
  SuccessGameEventId: 99F_MSQ_ER_FightLiang_success_mystic
  FailureGameEventId: ""
  ProgressionReward: ""
  ExperienceReward: ""
  ObjectiveReward: ""
  ItemRewardName: CRX_RewardContainerT5_Handwear_60
  ItemRewardQty: 1.0
  ShouldResetOnFactionChange: ""
  Repeatable: ""
  CanBeAbandoned: false
  Title: "@99F_MSQ08_FightLiang_title"
  Description: "@99F_MSQ08_FightLiang_desc"
  PlayerPrompt: "@99F_MSQ08_FightLiang_start_prompt"
  ObjectiveProposalResponse: "@99F_MSQ08_FightLiang_proposal"
  InProgressResponse: "@99F_MSQ08_FightLiang_incomplete"
  DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt: "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
  DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse: "@99F_MSQ08_FightLiang_complete"
  ObjectiveCompletionResponse: ""
  ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse: ""
  HideIncompleteTurninMarker: true
  ORMReleaseEventTags: ""
  ORMReleaseActiveOverride: ""
  SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid: ""
  EntitlementId: ""
  QuestArcTag: ""
  HideAvailableMapIcon: ""
  NOTE: Soul Trial alt
- ObjectiveID: 99F_MSQ_ER_FightLiang_occultist
  Type: MainStoryQuest
  Difficulty: ""
  DifficultyLevel: 59.0
  MaxInfluenceLevel: ""
  FlagPvp: ""
  CanBeShared: ""
  CanFastTravel: ""
  Task: 99F_MSQ_ER_FightLiang_container
  NpcDestinationId: 99F_Liang_01
  ExclusiveTerritory: ""
  AchievementId: 99F_MSQ_08
  RequiredAchievementId: 99F_MSQ_07 && Archetype_Occultist
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
  SuccessGameEventId: 99F_MSQ_ER_FightLiang_success_occultist
  FailureGameEventId: ""
  ProgressionReward: ""
  ExperienceReward: ""
  ObjectiveReward: ""
  ItemRewardName: CRX_RewardContainerT5_Handwear_60
  ItemRewardQty: 1.0
  ShouldResetOnFactionChange: ""
  Repeatable: ""
  CanBeAbandoned: false
  Title: "@99F_MSQ08_FightLiang_title"
  Description: "@99F_MSQ08_FightLiang_desc"
  PlayerPrompt: "@99F_MSQ08_FightLiang_start_prompt"
  ObjectiveProposalResponse: "@99F_MSQ08_FightLiang_proposal"
  InProgressResponse: "@99F_MSQ08_FightLiang_incomplete"
  DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt: "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
  DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse: "@99F_MSQ08_FightLiang_complete"
  ObjectiveCompletionResponse: ""
  ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse: ""
  HideIncompleteTurninMarker: true
  ORMReleaseEventTags: ""
  ORMReleaseActiveOverride: ""
  SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid: ""
  EntitlementId: ""
  QuestArcTag: ""
  HideAvailableMapIcon: ""
  NOTE: Soul Trial alt
- ObjectiveID: 99F_MSQ_ER_FightLiang_ranger
  Type: MainStoryQuest
  Difficulty: ""
  DifficultyLevel: 59.0
  MaxInfluenceLevel: ""
  FlagPvp: ""
  CanBeShared: ""
  CanFastTravel: ""
  Task: 99F_MSQ_ER_FightLiang_container
  NpcDestinationId: 99F_Liang_01
  ExclusiveTerritory: ""
  AchievementId: 99F_MSQ_08
  RequiredAchievementId: 99F_MSQ_07 && Archetype_Tracker
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
  SuccessGameEventId: 99F_MSQ_ER_FightLiang_success_ranger
  FailureGameEventId: ""
  ProgressionReward: ""
  ExperienceReward: ""
  ObjectiveReward: ""
  ItemRewardName: CRX_RewardContainerT5_Handwear_60
  ItemRewardQty: 1.0
  ShouldResetOnFactionChange: ""
  Repeatable: ""
  CanBeAbandoned: false
  Title: "@99F_MSQ08_FightLiang_title"
  Description: "@99F_MSQ08_FightLiang_desc"
  PlayerPrompt: "@99F_MSQ08_FightLiang_start_prompt"
  ObjectiveProposalResponse: "@99F_MSQ08_FightLiang_proposal"
  InProgressResponse: "@99F_MSQ08_FightLiang_incomplete"
  DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt: "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
  DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse: "@99F_MSQ08_FightLiang_complete"
  ObjectiveCompletionResponse: ""
  ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse: ""
  HideIncompleteTurninMarker: true
  ORMReleaseEventTags: ""
  ORMReleaseActiveOverride: ""
  SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid: ""
  EntitlementId: ""
  QuestArcTag: ""
  HideAvailableMapIcon: ""
  NOTE: Soul Trial alt
- ObjectiveID: 99F_MSQ_ER_FightLiang_soldier
  Type: MainStoryQuest
  Difficulty: ""
  DifficultyLevel: 59.0
  MaxInfluenceLevel: ""
  FlagPvp: ""
  CanBeShared: ""
  CanFastTravel: ""
  Task: 99F_MSQ_ER_FightLiang_container
  NpcDestinationId: 99F_Liang_01
  ExclusiveTerritory: ""
  AchievementId: 99F_MSQ_08
  RequiredAchievementId: 99F_MSQ_07 && Archetype_Mercenary
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
  SuccessGameEventId: 99F_MSQ_ER_FightLiang_success_soldier
  FailureGameEventId: ""
  ProgressionReward: ""
  ExperienceReward: ""
  ObjectiveReward: ""
  ItemRewardName: CRX_RewardContainerT5_Handwear_60
  ItemRewardQty: 1.0
  ShouldResetOnFactionChange: ""
  Repeatable: ""
  CanBeAbandoned: false
  Title: "@99F_MSQ08_FightLiang_title"
  Description: "@99F_MSQ08_FightLiang_desc"
  PlayerPrompt: "@99F_MSQ08_FightLiang_start_prompt"
  ObjectiveProposalResponse: "@99F_MSQ08_FightLiang_proposal"
  InProgressResponse: "@99F_MSQ08_FightLiang_incomplete"
  DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt: "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
  DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse: "@99F_MSQ08_FightLiang_complete"
  ObjectiveCompletionResponse: ""
  ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse: ""
  HideIncompleteTurninMarker: true
  ORMReleaseEventTags: ""
  ORMReleaseActiveOverride: ""
  SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid: ""
  EntitlementId: ""
  QuestArcTag: ""
  HideAvailableMapIcon: ""
  NOTE: Soul Trial alt
- ObjectiveID: 99F_MSQ_ER_FightLiang_swordsman
  Type: MainStoryQuest
  Difficulty: ""
  DifficultyLevel: 59.0
  MaxInfluenceLevel: ""
  FlagPvp: ""
  CanBeShared: ""
  CanFastTravel: ""
  Task: 99F_MSQ_ER_FightLiang_container
  NpcDestinationId: 99F_Liang_01
  ExclusiveTerritory: ""
  AchievementId: 99F_MSQ_08
  RequiredAchievementId: 99F_MSQ_07 && Archetype_Wanderer
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
  SuccessGameEventId: 99F_MSQ_ER_FightLiang_success_swordsman
  FailureGameEventId: ""
  ProgressionReward: ""
  ExperienceReward: ""
  ObjectiveReward: ""
  ItemRewardName: CRX_RewardContainerT5_Handwear_60
  ItemRewardQty: 1.0
  ShouldResetOnFactionChange: ""
  Repeatable: ""
  CanBeAbandoned: false
  Title: "@99F_MSQ08_FightLiang_title"
  Description: "@99F_MSQ08_FightLiang_desc"
  PlayerPrompt: "@99F_MSQ08_FightLiang_start_prompt"
  ObjectiveProposalResponse: "@99F_MSQ08_FightLiang_proposal"
  InProgressResponse: "@99F_MSQ08_FightLiang_incomplete"
  DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt: "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
  DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse: "@99F_MSQ08_FightLiang_complete"
  ObjectiveCompletionResponse: ""
  ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse: ""
  HideIncompleteTurninMarker: true
  ORMReleaseEventTags: ""
  ORMReleaseActiveOverride: ""
  SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid: ""
  EntitlementId: ""
  QuestArcTag: ""
  HideAvailableMapIcon: ""
  NOTE: Soul Trial alt
- ObjectiveID: 99F_MSQ_ER_ReuniteFamily
  Type: MainStoryQuest
  Difficulty: ""
  DifficultyLevel: 60.0
  MaxInfluenceLevel: ""
  FlagPvp: ""
  CanBeShared: ""
  CanFastTravel: ""
  Task: 99F_MSQ_ER_ReuniteFamily_container
  NpcDestinationId: 99F_Grace_08a
  ExclusiveTerritory: ""
  AchievementId: 99F_MSQ_09
  RequiredAchievementId: 99F_MSQ_08
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
  SuccessGameEventId: 99F_MSQ_ER_ReuniteFamily_success
  FailureGameEventId: ""
  ProgressionReward: ""
  ExperienceReward: ""
  ObjectiveReward: ""
  ItemRewardName: CRX_RewardContainerT5_Headgear_60
  ItemRewardQty: 1.0
  ShouldResetOnFactionChange: ""
  Repeatable: ""
  CanBeAbandoned: false
  Title: "@99F_MSQ09_ReuniteFamily_title"
  Description: "@99F_MSQ09_ReuniteFamily_desc"
  PlayerPrompt: "@99F_MSQ09_ReuniteFamily_start_prompt"
  ObjectiveProposalResponse: "@99F_MSQ09_ReuniteFamily_proposal"
  InProgressResponse: "@99F_MSQ09_ReuniteFamily_incomplete"
  DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt: "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
  DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse: "@99F_MSQ09_ReuniteFamily_complete"
  ObjectiveCompletionResponse: ""
  ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse: ""
  HideIncompleteTurninMarker: true
  ORMReleaseEventTags: ""
  ORMReleaseActiveOverride: ""
  SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid: ""
  EntitlementId: ""
  QuestArcTag: ""
  HideAvailableMapIcon: ""
  NOTE: ""
- ObjectiveID: 99F_MSQ_ER_StealBoat
  Type: MainStoryQuest
  Difficulty: ""
  DifficultyLevel: 60.0
  MaxInfluenceLevel: ""
  FlagPvp: ""
  CanBeShared: ""
  CanFastTravel: ""
  Task: 99F_MSQ_ER_StealBoat_container
  NpcDestinationId: 99F_Grace_09
  ExclusiveTerritory: ""
  AchievementId: 99F_MSQ_10
  RequiredAchievementId: 99F_MSQ_09
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
  SuccessGameEventId: 99F_MSQ_ER_StealBoat_success
  FailureGameEventId: ""
  ProgressionReward: ""
  ExperienceReward: ""
  ObjectiveReward: ""
  ItemRewardName: PotionHealthT5
  ItemRewardQty: 10.0
  ShouldResetOnFactionChange: ""
  Repeatable: ""
  CanBeAbandoned: false
  Title: "@99F_MSQ10_StealBoat_title"
  Description: "@99F_MSQ10_StealBoat_desc"
  PlayerPrompt: "@99F_MSQ10_StealBoat_start_prompt"
  ObjectiveProposalResponse: "@99F_MSQ10_StealBoat_proposal"
  InProgressResponse: "@99F_MSQ10_StealBoat_incomplete"
  DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt: "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
  DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse: "@99F_MSQ10_StealBoat_complete"
  ObjectiveCompletionResponse: ""
  ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse: ""
  HideIncompleteTurninMarker: true
  ORMReleaseEventTags: ""
  ORMReleaseActiveOverride: ""
  SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid: ""
  EntitlementId: ""
  QuestArcTag: ""
  HideAvailableMapIcon: ""
  NOTE: ""
- ObjectiveID: 99F_MSQ_ER_FightEmpress
  Type: MainStoryQuest
  Difficulty: ""
  DifficultyLevel: 60.0
  MaxInfluenceLevel: ""
  FlagPvp: ""
  CanBeShared: ""
  CanFastTravel: ""
  Task: 99F_MSQ_ER_FightEmpress_container
  NpcDestinationId: 99F_Sun_08
  ExclusiveTerritory: ""
  AchievementId: 99F_MSQ_11
  RequiredAchievementId: 99F_MSQ_10
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
  SuccessGameEventId: 99F_MSQ_ER_FightEmpress_success
  FailureGameEventId: ""
  ProgressionReward: ""
  ExperienceReward: ""
  ObjectiveReward: ""
  ItemRewardName: ""
  ItemRewardQty: null
  ShouldResetOnFactionChange: ""
  Repeatable: ""
  CanBeAbandoned: false
  Title: "@99F_MSQ11_FightEmpress_title"
  Description: "@99F_MSQ11_FightEmpress_desc"
  PlayerPrompt: "@99F_MSQ11_FightEmpress_start_prompt"
  ObjectiveProposalResponse: "@99F_MSQ11_FightEmpress_proposal"
  InProgressResponse: "@99F_MSQ11_FightEmpress_incomplete"
  DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt: "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
  DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse: "@99F_MSQ11_FightEmpress_complete"
  ObjectiveCompletionResponse: ""
  ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse: ""
  HideIncompleteTurninMarker: true
  ORMReleaseEventTags: ""
  ORMReleaseActiveOverride: ""
  SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid: ""
  EntitlementId: ""
  QuestArcTag: ""
  HideAvailableMapIcon: ""
  NOTE: Soul Trial
- ObjectiveID: 99F_MSQ_ER_DeliverPoem
  Type: MainStoryQuest
  Difficulty: ""
  DifficultyLevel: 60.0
  MaxInfluenceLevel: ""
  FlagPvp: ""
  CanBeShared: ""
  CanFastTravel: ""
  Task: 99F_MSQ_ER_DeliverPoem_container
  NpcDestinationId: 99F_Yash_03
  ExclusiveTerritory: ""
  AchievementId: 99F_MSQ_12
  RequiredAchievementId: 99F_MSQ_11
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
  SuccessGameEventId: 99F_MSQ_ER_DeliverPoem_success
  FailureGameEventId: ""
  ProgressionReward: ""
  ExperienceReward: ""
  ObjectiveReward: ""
  ItemRewardName: CRX_RewardContainerT5_Weapons_60
  ItemRewardQty: 1.0
  ShouldResetOnFactionChange: ""
  Repeatable: ""
  CanBeAbandoned: false
  Title: "@99F_MSQ12_DeliverPoem_title"
  Description: "@99F_MSQ12_DeliverPoem_desc"
  PlayerPrompt: "@99F_MSQ12_DeliverPoem_start_prompt"
  ObjectiveProposalResponse: "@99F_MSQ12_DeliverPoem_proposal"
  InProgressResponse: "@99F_MSQ12_DeliverPoem_incomplete"
  DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt: "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
  DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse: "@99F_MSQ12_DeliverPoem_complete"
  ObjectiveCompletionResponse: ""
  ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse: ""
  HideIncompleteTurninMarker: true
  ORMReleaseEventTags: ""
  ORMReleaseActiveOverride: ""
  SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid: ""
  EntitlementId: ""
  QuestArcTag: ""
  HideAvailableMapIcon: ""
  NOTE: ""
